GITHUB LINKEDIN PORTFOLIO E-MAIL 343-202-0214

### **PROFILE**

Talented and experienced front-end developer with 2+ years of experience executing with plenty of diverse skills. Experience has taught me to take accessibility and responsiveness seriously, and I am delighted to continue my career with a focus on the web readily accessible, entirely responsive, and intuitive for users.

# **EDUCATION**

- Algonquin College, Ottawa Interactive Media Design 2021 - Present
- 2. Maharaja Sayajirao University, India Communications, 2016 2019

### **SKILLS**

- HTML/CSS / TAILWIND CSS
- JavaScript
- React / React Native
- Github
- SQL
- Sanity
- Solidity

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- <u>Design Thinking and Innovation by Harvard</u> <u>Business School Online</u>
- Certified in Mailchimp Foundations by MailChimp
- Certified in Digital Marketing by Accenture
- IBM Certified in Enterprise Design Thinking, Co-Creator and Practitioner.
- Google Certified in the Fundamentals of Digital Marketing
- <u>Certified in Introduction to Business Management by King's College London</u>

#### **EXPERIENCE**

SALES ASSOCIATE, CANADIAN TIRE, CARLING AVENUE – 2021 – PRESENT

Identifying low stock levels and maintain inventory accuracy. Ensuring that retail basics tasks are executed efficiently. Answering questions and providing friendly advice and services to customers. Responding to and handling customer inquiries, requests and concerns in a timely manner, over the phone and in person. Locating products in the warehouse. Meeting and greeting customers and providing friendly, informed service to them. Guiding customer to the location of requested items.

SALES ASSOCIATE, BOMBAY SPICES, WEST HUNT CLUB ROAD – 2021 – 2021

Followed department protocols for product preparation, storage, rotation, and stocking. Product quality and freshness are monitored, and adequate product rotation is ensured. Helped with inventory inspections on a regular basis. Arrives on time, well groomed, clothed, and prepared to work; performs all planned shifts and attends mandatory trainings and meetings. Provided exceptional customer service, handled client requirements in a fast and effective manner, and modelled suggestive selling strategies; promptly and courteously answered phones and emails. Maintained a clean and hygienic working and shopping environment; by keeping equipment clean and safe in compliance with WFM cleanliness and safety requirements..

CASHIER, CIRCLE K, WALKLEY ROAD -2020 -2021

Stocked shelves, kept the store clean, and took away the trash at the end of the shift. Pulled out expired items and storing them in a separate room, as well as reconciling lottery and paperwork at the conclusion of each shift.

GITHUB LINKEDIN PORTFOLIO E-MAIL 343-202-0214